https://www.lamkingrips.com/privacy-policy/

SHOP
Search for:
LAMKIN CORPORATION PRIVACY POLICY
We may from time to time update this Policy. We will notify you of changes to the Policy by posting the updated Policy on this page. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of the Policy.
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Lamkin collects two types of information during your visits to our Site. First, we collect non-personally identifiable information. When visitors come to our Site, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages of the Site were visited, the order in which they were visited and which links were “clicked.” Collecting such information involves logging the IP addresses. Although such information is not personally identifiable, it may be possible to determine from an IP address a visitor’s Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of the visitor’s point of connectivity.
We also use “cookies” and other tracking technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information regarding you. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser. Cookies make it possible for us to recognize your browser when you visit our Site. By doing this, we can personalize your return visits and save you time during login and checkout. Your browser must be set to accept cookies in order for you to enjoy the benefits of being a registered user of the Site.
Second, we collect personal and personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, credit card number and information concerning products and services purchased through the Site.
How We Use Collected InformationPlease take some time to familiarize yourself with the different ways that Lamkin uses the information that we gather. Keep in mind that, while we encourage all third parties involved in running our business to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our visitors and to otherwise handle personally identifiable information in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from Lamkin or independently.
Non-personally identifiable informationLamkin uses non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address and the pages that you visit on our Site, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Site and improve Site-related services and features. Your IP address and other non-personally identifiable information also may be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and Site usage trends. This information aids us in merchandising and in developing the design and layout of the Site.
We also may share aggregated statistical data and other non-personally identifiable information with our current and potential business partners, and with our service providers.
Personally identifiable informationLamkin uses personally identifiable information collected from you to:
complete transactions initiated by you (such as the sale of products);
get in touch with you when necessary;
respond to your requests;
contact you to make sure you are satisfied with our products or to find out how we can serve you better;
conduct in-depth marketing research regarding our customers and potential customers;
offer you product upgrades; and financial information (credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, and so forth) are used to bill you for products sold.
Our Site presently does not store your credit card information, and any of your credit card information that may be stored in other Lamkin systems is protected by state-of-the-art firewalls.
You may, from time to time, receive information from us via email or mailings regarding new features, new products and services and special offers we think you’ll find valuable. If you’d like to opt out of receiving future emails or mailings from Lamkin, please follow the procedure outlined in the Choice/Opt-out section below.
Lamkin also may use your personally identifiable information to “pre-populate” forms that are used by the Site to facilitate transactions with us. Other types of use by us of personally identifiable information are discussed below.
SERVICE PROVIDERS
We work with third parties who provide services, including but not limited to order processing and fulfillment, credit card clearance, e-commerce affiliation, data analysis and other services of an administrative nature. Personally identifiable information, including financial information, is shared with such third parties for the purpose of providing such services.
Further, we may use selected reputable third parties for marketing and analysis purposes. Some of these third parties may be given access to some, or all, of the information that you provide to us and may use cookies or other tracking technologies in connection with providing their services. To the extent that we provide your personally identifiable information to such third parties, we seek to restrict their ability to use such information for their own marketing purposes; however, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such third parties.
SALE OF OUR COMPANY
As a natural consequence of the development of our company, we could be sold to another company. In the event that we are acquired by another company or a significant portion of our assets is sold to another company, all of the customer information including both financial records and consumer information that we have collected may be transferred to the new company.
CHOICE/OPT-OUT
We do not disclose an individual customer’s personally identifiable information to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes if we have received and processed a request from that customer not to have his or her personal information shared for this purpose. In addition, we also allow you to decide to “opt-out” from receiving further marketing information directly from us. You may submit this type of opt-out request by using our unsubscribe form Click here to remove your name from our list, or let us know by contacting us by any of the means set forth in the “Contacting Lamkin” section below and telling us that you do not want to receive promotional e-mail or other mail from Lamkin and/or you don’t want your personally identifiable information shared with third parties for third party direct marketing purposes. If you elect to opt-out, supplied e-mail addresses on our customer registration form will be used for order confirmation and alerts relating to an order.
ONLINE SURVEYS
Lamkin sometimes administers online surveys in connection with the Site in which we ask you for demographic information and opinions. We do not ask you for personally identifiable information as part of a survey. We use the collected survey data on an aggregated basis to better understand the needs of all of our customers.
CERTAIN NON-MARKETING USES
Lamkin may send to you periodic announcements regarding status updates, service changes concerning the Site and other administrative matters.
Subject to applicable law, we reserve the right to release information concerning any Site visitor where such visitor is believed to be in violation of his or her obligations to us, is partaking (or is suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, in response to civil subpoenas and discovery requests, to protect the interests of Lamkin, our customers or others, and as otherwise permitted or required by law.
THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
Emails from Lamkin or its business partners, and the Site itself, may contain links to other Internet websites, including sites that may or may not be owned or operated by Lamkin. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such sites’ use of any information (such as IP number) collected when email recipients or Site visitors click through links to those sites. If you visit such websites, we encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of the sites.
HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS STORED
Lamkin seeks to use reasonable security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information that is under our control. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use and confidentiality of information, either for our own purposes or on behalf of our customers, Lamkin has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we process. Personal information you reveal to us is protected during transmission by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information and is the accepted standard industry-wide for web site security (click here for more details). Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of the foregoing, while we seek to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and Lamkin’s servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the Site. You provide all such information at your own risk.
HOW TO UPDATE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
If you have signed up for an account with Lamkin, you may update your mailing address, email address, name changes, or other information by contacting us at the phone numbers listed above.
CONTACTING LAMKIN
If you have any questions about this Policy, the data collection and usage practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, or if you wish to report a violation of this Policy, please contact us. We can be reached through our Contact us page, or you can reach us from the United States or Canada by telephone at 800-642-7755 between the hours of 8am – 4:30pm PST on Monday through Thursday and 8am-4pm PST on Fridays, or by fax at 1-619-661-0014. International calls can be placed to 800-642-7755. Our postal address is: 6530 Gateway Park Drive, San Diego, CA 92154. Please allow up to two weeks for your request to be processed.
QUALITY CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE
Lamkin is committed to quality customer experience. We are constantly reviewing your feedback to improve and enhance your user experience. You can tell us what you think by contacting our customer support department at 800-642-7755.
X
NOTICE: The Lamkin eCommerce functionality is undergoing some changes and will be available again in January 2021. Please email customerservice@lamkingrips.com with any question.
